{
    "id": "2ea73ba2151e41329efdffb95481337e",
    "title": "This, That, These And Those",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "................................... were the best days of my life.",
            "description": "That and those refer to situations that are over.",
            "answers": [
                "Those",
                "That",
                "These"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e1e4fc2907c942879a99d99ab7c9ed85"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. says that he wants to watch a movie.",
            "description": "This cannot be used without a noun when it refers to people.",
            "answers": [
                "This",
                "This boy",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "039a67c89b2d4269a22a32492a7203c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Put …………………….. down – they are dirty.",
            "description": "When this, that, these and those refer to things, they can be used with or without articles.",
            "answers": [
                "those",
                "those clothes",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a45136e168a843b3a2b5ba8dc35701ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… is very tasty. Can I have some more?",
            "description": "We use this to talk about people and things which are close to us.",
            "answers": [
                "This",
                "That",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d10ccb2af33340deabd58e2dce752af5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Get ……………………….. cat off the piano.",
            "description": "We use that and those to talk about people and things which are away from us.",
            "answers": [
                "this",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e2bbb08db149443dbe5fcd0a86d9dad0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know what I am doing in ……………………. company.",
            "description": "Here the present continuous verb clearly indicates that we are talking about something that is going on at the moment. We use this and these in these contexts.",
            "answers": [
                "this",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10bc61b14a1141fda02f15e07f0aa63d"
        },
        {
            "question": "All the time I worked at …………………….. company I hated it.",
            "description": "That and those refer to situations that are over.",
            "answers": [
                "this",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f9f921719cc4576b439eefd2e3d7dc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "You shouldn’t have behaved like ……………………….",
            "description": "That and those refer to situations that are over.",
            "answers": [
                "this",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "274295e4883e494c8c8e0adccf3b7e1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "A dog’s intelligence is much greater than ………………………..",
            "description": "That and those are often used with a following description to mean ‘the ones’.",
            "answers": [
                "a cat",
                "that of a cat",
                "this of a cat"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7ed162d476b47e09eff52bd604b02cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. who have not yet registered should do so immediately.",
            "description": "Those who means the people who. These cannot be used with this meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "Those",
                "These",
                "That"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b50087b1138f41a1bc72359269cc41c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was so cold ………………………… I could see my breath.",
            "description": "We use that in the conjunction so…that.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "this",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2e1fd940dcd44cc5a335a0c439828c73"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘How was the movie?’ ‘Not all ………………………. good.’",
            "description": "Not all that can mean not very.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "this"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "13d2f3d05d2a4cccaac6c67ac1ac11e6"
        }
    ]
}